deltavacations.com 2009-06-29

# Delta Vacations - Privacy Policy

| 

### Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions, collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our website.

**I. Security**  
When you send confidential data to us on an Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions, website, we require that a "secure session" first be established using Secure Socket Layer (SSL), or Secure Electronic Transaction (SET) protocol when that is fully available. For further information about SSL, SET and the safety and confidentiality of personal data transmissions over the Internet, please read our Security Q&A.

**II. Information Collection**  
When you browse any Travel Impressions website, you do so anonymously. Personal information -- including your E-mail address -- is not collected. Some of our websites, however, may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your E-mail address for purposes such as correspondence, or participating in online surveys. Like many other commercial websites, the Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions, website may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our site is used. Please read About Cookies for more information.

**III. Information Use**  
If you provide us with your E-mail address, or have done so in the past, we may upon occasion send you E-mail offers. We may use information you have given us only for the purpose of sending you advertising information pertaining to Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions.

**IV. Declining E-mail Offers**  
Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions, provides customers with an easy means to decline receiving E-mail offers. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers from us by simply replying to the E-mail and informing us of your preferences. All E-mail offers that you receive from Travel Impressions will inform you of how to decline receiving further E-mail advertisements.

**V. Children**  
Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions, does not knowingly solicit data from children, and we do not knowingly market to children.

**VI. Company Commitment to Policy**  
In keeping with our long-standing leadership in consumer Privacy protection, Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions, is actively involved with current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet and in all aspects of electronic commerce.

Delta Vacations, operated by Travel Impressions, assists you in finding travel suppliers and making arrangements that meet your individual needs. We consider various factors in identifying travel suppliers to you and recommending specific itineraries. In this role, we are acting as an independent third party and not as a fiduciary. We want you to be aware that certain suppliers pay us commissions as well as incentives for reaching sales targets or other goals, and from time to time may also provide incentives to our travel counselors. Certain suppliers may also provide compensation to us for various marketing and administrative services that we perform for them, such as granting them access to our marketing channels, participating in marketing programs and supporting technology initiatives. From time to time we may enter into other business relationships with suppliers and these arrangements, including levels and types of compensation and incentives we receive, are subject to change. In identifying suppliers and recommending itineraries, we may consider a number of factors, including supplier availability and your preferences. The relationships we have with suppliers may also influence the suppliers we identify and the itineraries we recommend.   
  
---|---
